[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The members of this band included Sgt. Floyd   Pepers, Janice, Zoot, Animal, and Lips.", "correct_answer": "Dr. Teeth and Electric Mayhem", "incorrect_answers": ["The  Zoot Sims Big Band", "The Fabulous Baker brothers", "Nylon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Belgian artist dedicated his life to painting roses and other flowers and plants?", "correct_answer": "Pierre-Joseph Redoute", "incorrect_answers": ["Claude Monet", "Paul Cezanne", "Pierre-Auguste Renoir"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This European country is divided into three districts, 12 cantons, and 116 communes.", "correct_answer": "Luxembourg", "incorrect_answers": ["Belgium", "Andorra", "Switzerland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the card game Texas hold em, the last community card to hit the table is referred to as what?", "correct_answer": "The river", "incorrect_answers": ["Fourth street", "The turn", "The flop"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Antigua and Barbuda, Belize, and Zimbabwe are three countries which share just one of these four items.", "correct_answer": "Independence gained from the UK", "incorrect_answers": ["Population less than 30,000 people", "Currency", "Border"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following was not a result of the War of the Roses?", "correct_answer": "The defeat of the Spanish Armada", "incorrect_answers": ["The end of the feudal powers of British nobles", "Henry VII took power in England.", "A strong central government in England"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many species of elephant exist today?", "correct_answer": "3", "incorrect_answers": ["1", "6", "5"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The poor man! He was diagnosed a bilateeral perobital hematoma. What does he have?", "correct_answer": "Two black eye", "incorrect_answers": ["Halitosis", "Two hernias", "A tumor in the center of the brain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which statement about the actor Donald Sutherland is untrue?", "correct_answer": "He was born in Teddington, Middlesex, England.", "incorrect_answers": ["He starred as Casanova in Il Casanova di Federico Fellini", "He starred as Homer Simpson.", "He starred in Alex in Wonderland, which featured Federico Fellini"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is a major lightsaber battle in every Star Wars film. Where did the one in the film, The Empire Strikes Back take place?", "correct_answer": "Cloud City", "incorrect_answers": ["Hoth", "Imperial Star Destroyer", "Death Star"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What country is the largest producer of strawberries in the world?", "correct_answer": "United States", "incorrect_answers": ["Spain", "South Korea", "France"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The earliest evidence of animal life comes from this period.", "correct_answer": "Vendian", "incorrect_answers": ["Cambrian", "Ordovician", "Carboniferous"]}]